vac-ban.com 2018-03-15

# VAC-BAN.com - CS:GO stats tracking & VAC ban notifications

This privacy policy outlines how information collected through our site is both used and protected. Information which we request from users, or information that is made available to us will be used with accordance to this policy.

**Information Collected**  
You will never be asked to provide any of your personal information to access our services.

We only collect your steam profile ID and the name of your account to enhance data shown on the website.

**Use of Non-Personal Information**  
We also collect non-personal information whenever you interact with our service. Non-personal identification information may include another profile of a user you maybe searching. This information is to enhance the service and cannot ber linked directly back to you.

**Cookies**  
Our website may use "cookies" to enhance your experience. Your web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly.

**Data Protection**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal account on the website.

**Sharing Information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent any personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

This policy was last modified on August 29, 2015.
